Aaron Bushman

Full Stack Developer

Aaron Bushman

3318 Rosewood Ave Richmond, VA 23221

804-252-7587 aaronbushman@gmail.com www.aaron-bushman.com/

Skills

I have experience utilizing front and back end programming languages and technologies such as JavaScript, JQuery, React, Nodejs, MySQL, MongoDB, Handlebars, HTML, CSS among others from just completing a coding bootcamp at the University of Richmond

I have a decade of experience in management with the Sherwin-Williams Company where I won multiple management and sales awards with strong yearly sales gains.

Experience

Sherwin-Williams Company / Store Manager

October 2012 - April 2019, Richmond, Virginia

I managed a staff of employees and worked directly with large accounts building relationships and growing sales. During this time, I won multiple "Masters" awards among other accolades.

Sherwin-Williams Company / Assistant Store Manager

December 2008 - September 2012, Richmond, Virginia

I entered the company through their management training program for college graduates.

Education

University of Richmond Coding Bootcamp

May 2019 - October 2019

An intense program that taught me the ins and outs of full stack development. I learned JavaScript, JQuery, React, Nodejs, MySql, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, among others and was able to put together a portfolio from my studies and experience.

Virginia Commonwealth University / B.A. in Art History

August 2002 - May 2007, Richmond, Virginia

I received a broad education at VCU with studies focused on modern and contemporary art history.

Personal Projects

I am currently building and researching for the "Virginia Soul Archive" which is a Mongo database detailing all of the known commercial releases of soul and r&b music from Virginia based musicians from the 1950s-1980s. I plan for it to be publicly accessible by the end of 2019 through a MERN app deployed on AWS.